# Isabelle Björklund

1995 01 02 Batterigatan 4C, 415 16 Göteborg isabelle.bjorklund@gmail.com +46 704212202

Link to portfolio: is abelle bjorklund.com/is abelle-portfolio.pdf



I am a driven UX/UI designer with broad expertise in usability and product development. I have a special interest in user behavior and understand the importance of valid data.

I have experience working with websites and online stores, as well as product development of new and existing systems. To create prototypes and optimal solutions, I use heories, analysis and knowledge.

With a keen ear for customer needs, I understand how to help interpret and shape initial intentions to a great product that reaches the end user. I will be a valuable asset in your team, since I have experience in delivering both creative and systematic solutions against short lead times.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor in fine arts- Product design2013-2016

Linnaeus University, Kalmar

Exchange semester 2015-2016

ITU- Istanbul Technical University, Istanbul

#### SKILLS

#### Adobe

Photoshop Illustrator Indesign Premiere Pro

# Design & prototyping

Sketch Invision Figma

# Other merits

App project in my spare time (UX role)

Design mentor

Project manager for events and arrangements

Basic CSS (beginner)

Driver's license

#### Methods

Project management
Product development
Wireframing
Usability studies
User research
Prototyping
Field studies

# Characteristics

Problem solver
Adaptable
Communicative
Result oriented
User-centered
Reliable
Enjoys responsibility and challenges.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

UX Designerfeb 2020-

Sigma it, Göteborg

Consultant at Sigma IT, responsibilities including delivering UX-work and UI for an inhouse project, working with app-development.

# UI, UX & Graphic Designerjan 2017- feb 2020

HL Design & Media, Växjö

Developing new digital products and improvements for a wide range of clients in areas as education, public sector and industry to name a few.

Responsibilities including delivering UX-work and UI, to create solutions that give value for the user, and the client's business. This by improving and creating new websites, webshops and custom systems. In addition to designing, the work also involves client contact, project leading and planning.

#### Internship

oct 2016- dec 2016

HL Design & Media, Växjö

My time as an intern involved a lot of UX-work, testing and market research. I was introduced to the world of web design and marketing. I got the opportunity to design UI for some projects and learn basic HTML & CSS.

# TED X

2016- one week workshop

Collab. between LNU, KTH and JIBS, Värnamo

A collaboration with engineers from KTH and economists from JIBS. We stayed in Värnamo for one week, working with concept developing for the company 3M.